<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rmenn - personal blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.rmenn.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on rmenn - personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rmenn&#34;&gt;Rahul Menon&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 19:53:09 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.rmenn.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Running bootkube on OSX</title>
      <link>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/bootkube-coseos-osx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 19:53:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/bootkube-coseos-osx/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d heard of bootkube and wanted to try it out, I also really wanted to run this locally on my MacBook. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to run it on Virtual Box, this was when I remembered kubesolo which used the xhvye virtualization to stand up a kubernetes cluster on your MacBook. I then looked and found corectl, which allows you to run a coreos vm on xhyve. It took me a day or so to figure out how exactly I needed to bring up the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootkube</title>
      <link>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/bootkube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 21:31:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/bootkube/</guid>
      <description>I have been trying out bootkube for a while now. It may be a beta, but I love the concept and how it works.
For those who have not heard about bootkube, its a tool which is used to bootstrap self-hosted clusters. Self-hosted essentially means running kubernetes as a objects on the kubernetes cluster ( I can hear people close their tabs ), its just kubernetes running on kubernetes. You can take a look at this video where Aaron Levy explains what self-hosted is and how you can benefit from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here we Go</title>
      <link>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 15:29:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.rmenn.in/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, and welcome to my space. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to drop a few pearls of wisdom here, but this is also a record of my misadventures and here&amp;rsquo;s hoping nobody repeats them!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>